sweetfreestuff.com 2016-11-23

# Privacy Policy – SweetFreeStuff.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at <http://www.sweetfreestuff.com/contact/>.

At SweetFreeStuff.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by SweetFreeStuff.com and how we use it.

**Cookies**

SweetFreeStuff.com uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on SweetFreeStuff.com.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to SweetFreeStuff.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Our Advertising Partners**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

Some of our advertising partners include:

_Click the links above to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of SweetFreeStuff.com._

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on SweetFreeStuff.com and which are sent directly to your browser.

They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

SweetFreeStuff.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Third Party Privacy Policies**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. SweetFreeStuff.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. [What Are Cookies?](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies)

**Consent**

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

**Affiliate Disclosure**

This website contains Affiliate links. The affiliate links are in the form of Banner Ads, and Text Links. We receive a commission on offers via the hypertext link to our vendor partner. Clicks are tracked by means of a code that is contained in our Affiliate links.

**Newsletter Subscription**

All of our newsletters are opt-in, meaning that they are sent only to those who have specifically requested to receive them.

Unsubscribe instructions are included at the bottom of each issue. Some newsletter issues include advertising, clearly identified as such.

By signing up to receive our email newsletters, you also agree to receive occasional email announcements and special offers from our partners.

No information gathered from newsletter subscribers, including email addresses, is ever shared with or sold to any third party, unless expressly requested by the user.

**Update**

This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Sunday, March 22nd, 2015.

_Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here._
